搞什么啊 迦勒？
What the fuck, Caleb?
等着看我拍到的镜头吧
Oh, wait till you see the shot I got.
你看上去像是屎都被吓出来了
You looked like you were gonna shit a brick out sideways.
你差点把我的脑袋削掉
You could have taken my head off.
那些螺旋桨太钝 削不利落的
It wouldn't have been a clean decapitation with these blades.
顶多是把你的脸削个稀烂
You'd just scramble your face up real good.
难道你不该去看看 洁西卡好点了没有吗？
Shouldn't you go see if Jessica is feeling any better?
她会没事的 我给了她一粒镇静药
She'll be fine. I gave her Klonopin
不管她哪里不舒服 睡醒后就会好了
so she can sleep off whatever the fuck is wrong with her.
那妞真是麻烦
Girl is such a pain in the ass.
洁西卡？
Jessica?
嘿
Hey.
表姐 你好点了吗？
How you feeling, cuz?
既然你们其他那些朋友都没来
Since none of these other friends of yours bothered to show up,
我能借你的车逃离这里 免得跟你的新男友困在一起
can I take your car and escape the hell of being stuck here
受地狱般的煎熬吗？
with your latest boyfriend?
聊得真愉快
Great chat.
你最好在接下来的半小时内醒过来
You better wake up in the next half hour
否则我就不得不 淹死那个无脑的可怜虫了
or I'm gonna be forced to go drown that brainless meat puppet's sorry ass.
(艾米莉勃朗特 《呼啸山庄》)
(“让我进去!”)
“噩梦般强烈的恐惧笼罩着我
"The intense horror of my nightmare came over me."
我试图缩回我的手臂 但那只手紧紧抓住了它
"I tried to draw back my arm but the hand clung on
接着一个最忧郁的声音开始抽泣
and a most melancholy voice sobbed,
'让我进去
'Let me in.'"
让我进去！'
"'Let me in!'"
伴随着呼喊声 我模糊地辨认出
"As it spoke, I discerned, obscurely
一张孩子的脸正透过窗户往里看
a child's face looking through the window."
我发现光靠挣扎无法摆脱那怪物
"Finding it useless to attempt shaking the creature off,
于是就把它的手腕 往碎玻璃那里拉…”
I pulled its wrist on to the broken pane…"
洁西？
Jess?
-“…然后来回摩擦…” -请别再背了
-"…and rubbed it to and fro…" -Please shut up.
“…直到鲜血流下来 浸湿了床单
"…till the blood ran down and soaked the bedclothes."
但它仍在哀号着：'让我进去！'”
"Yet still it wailed,  'Let me in!'"
洁西卡！
Jessica!
糟糕！
Shit, shit, shit!
见鬼！
不要啊 洁西？
No, Jess. Jess? Jess?
这下 谁是无脑的可怜虫？
Who's the brainless meat puppet now?
迦勒
Caleb.
搞什么？
What the fuck?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
发生什么事了？
What the hell happened?
洁西？
Jess?
洁西卡？
Jessica?
什么鬼？
What the fuck? What?
怎么会这样？ 不要…
No, no, no…
迦勒！
Caleb!
不要
No…
不 迦勒！
No, Caleb!
迦勒！
Caleb!
(一天前)
(验孕棒)
贝丝！
Beth!
贝丝 你在里头吗？
Beth, you in there?
给我五分钟 好吗？
Just give me five, all right?
布兰登正在大发雷霆
Brandon is losing his shit.
他找不到昨晚扳手腕比赛中
He can't find the Strat he won
赢到的斯特拉托卡西特吉他了
in that arm wrestling contest last night.
那把吉他我已经调好了音 放在了舞台左侧
It's already tuned and racked stage left
正如我半小时前告诉过你的那样
like I told you it was half an hour ago.
你没事吧？
You feeling all right in there?
我挺好
I'm fine.
回你的位置上去就是
Just go man your station.
开幕前我会回去的
I'll be back before curtains up.
明白了 老大
You got it, boss.
见过我最喜欢的黑色T恤吗？
Have you seen my favorite black t-shirt?
明天的劳动节抗议活动我要穿的
I need it for the Labor Day protest tomorrow.
(艾莉之墨 文身)
妈妈？
Mom?
你不能独自去参加什么抗议
You're not going to any protest on your own.
索菲的爸爸会带我们去的 我大概已经告诉过你十遍了
Sophie's dad's taking us. I've told you, like, ten times already.
记得吗？
Remember?
你有记得去浴室的洗衣篮里找过吗？
Well, did you remember to check the bathroom hamper?
让丹尼把音乐关小点
Tell Danny to turn the music down.
妈妈叫你把音乐关小点！
Mom says, "Turn the music down!"
如果要这样吼 我不会自己吼啊？
I could've done that myself!
卡西 我的剪刀 该不会是在你那儿吧？
Kassie, you better not have my scissors.
不在我这儿 妈妈！
Don't got 'em, Mom!
(家 甜蜜的家)
T恤是脏的
It's dirty.
把它跟要洗的衣服放在一起 我稍后会洗的
Well, stick it in the laundry, and I'll do it later.
你会忘记的 你老是忘记
You'll forget. You always forget.
你知道洗衣机在哪儿 可以自己洗
You know where the washing machine is.
嘿 布里奇特 我妈今天上晚班
Hey, Bridget. Mom's on nights
我们打算刷《半夜鬼上床》系列电影
and we're watching all the Freddy movies in a row.
-差劲的几部也刷 -那个系列没差劲的
-Even the shitty ones. -There aren't any shitty ones.
所以 你想不想过来…
So, you, um, wanna come over and…
做梦吧你
In your dreams.
你的男朋友都是怪人
Your boyfriends are weirdos.
你才是怪人
You're the weirdo.
卡西！
Kassie!
今晚的听众很多吗 丹？
Big crowd in tonight, Dan?
-出去 布里奇特！ -我也想 可是…
-Get out, Bridge! -I would, but--
让我进去！
Let me in!
谁去应一下门好吗？
Somebody get that, please!
行了 来了！
All right, all right!
嘭！
Boo!
贝丝
Beth.
你坏死了
You bitch.
惊喜吧 姐？
Surprise, sis.
你什么时候进的城？
When did you get into town?
我是从洛杉矶国际机场 直接乘优步到这里的
I Uber'd straight here from LAX.
你最近睡觉了吗？你看上去真像妈妈
You been sleeping? You look like Mom.
总比你看上去像卫生棉条强
Beats looking like a tampon.
楼下的门禁系统坏了
You know, the downstairs buzzer is totally busted.
我是从大街上直接走进来的
I was able to walk in right off the street.
这栋楼没一样东西是好的
Whole building's busted.
一个月后就会被拆掉了
It's getting knocked in a month.
你是开玩笑的吧
You're kidding me.
不是 我们要被赶出去了
Nope. We're out.
你们找到新住处了吗？
Have you guys found a new place?
还没
Not yet.
见鬼 艾尔 你和阿捷一直都住在这里
Shit, El. You and Jay have been here forever.
曼谷棒不棒？
Was Bangkok awesome?
棒极了 那里有疯狂痴迷的粉丝
Insane. Crazy, obsessive fans over there.
你喝过蛇血了吗？
Did you drink snake blood?
嘿 这问题太不尊重他国文化了
Hey, that's culturally insensitive.
那猴脑烧烤呢？
What about monkey brain barbecue?
见鬼 丹 这问题没好多少
Oh, yeah. That's so much better, Dan.
卡西 你的这个朋友是谁？
Who's your friend, Kass?
她叫斯塔法尼
She's called Staffanie.
你好 斯塔法尼
Oh. Hey, Staffanie.
她这是怎么回事？
What's her, uh, situation?
丹尼告诉我 这栋楼以前是家银行
Danny told me that when this building used to be a bank,
当年有个出纳员偷钱被抓 然后上吊自杀了
a teller got caught stealing and hunged himself
如果你口袋里揣着硬币 在楼里四处走动
and if you walk around with coins in your pockets,
他的鬼魂会听到叮当声
his ghost hears the jingle.
然后他就会把你吓死 拿走你所有的钱
And he scares you to death so he can take all your money.
这是真的
It's true.
如果他来找我 斯塔法尼就会先把他吓死
If he comes after me, Staffanie will scare him to death first.
世上根本没有鬼
Ghosts aren't real.
你见过鬼吗？
Have you ever seen one?
那你怎么知道他们不存在呢？
Then how do you know they don't exist?
因为
Because…
我只相信我能看到的东西
I only believe what I can see.
给我的？
For me?
只给酷酷的摇滚小妞
It's for badass rock chicks only.
看呀 妈妈 我很酷
Look, Mom. I'm a badass.
请别教唆她加入你那骨肉皮的世界
Please don't indoctrinate her into your groupie world.
什么是“骨肉皮”？
What's a groupie?
那是你妈妈最喜欢给我取的昵称
Your mom's favorite nickname for me,
虽然她知道我是吉他技师
even though she knows I'm a guitar technician.
随你怎么说
If you say so.
嘿 友好一点 不然你就得不到礼物了
Hey, be nice or you don't get a gift.
说到这个 看看我给你爸买了什么
Speaking of which, check out what I got your dad.
(懒人的啤酒杯)
怎么了 艾尔？
What's going on, El?
丹尼 开我的车 跟姐姐妹妹一起去买披萨
Danny, go take my car and get pizza with your sisters.
没问题 妈妈
Sure thing, Mom.
我就是不明白怎么会这样
I just can't wrap my head around all this.
怎么？他在外头有人了？
What, did he meet someone else?
不是
No.
他认为支付子女抚养费 就等同于远距离共同抚养
He believes paying child support equals co-parenting from afar.
你怎么没告诉我呢 艾尔？
Why didn't you tell me, El?
我要知道 就会立马跳上飞机 赶来帮你解决这个问题
I would've jumped right on a plane to help you work through this.
我打过电话给你
I called you.
打了两次
Twice.
第一次是他告诉我他要离开的时候
First time, when he told me he was leaving.
第二次是他搬出去的那天晚上
Second, the night he moved out.
那是两个半月前的事了 贝丝
That was two and half months ago, Beth.
对不起 好吗？
I'm sorry, okay?
你也知道 巡演时我会全情投入
You know when I'm on the road, I get sucked in deep
我正在努力争取首席技师的位子
and I'm trying to make chief tech right now.
如果成功了 我将成为乐队中 第一个当上首席的女性 所以…
And if I do, I'll be the first woman in my crew to do it, so…
求你了 艾莉 这件事我们得好好谈谈
Please, Ellie, we need to talk this through properly.
艾尔
El…
听着 今晚你可以睡在沙发上
Look, you can sleep on the sofa tonight
但我得打包 准备搬走
but I gotta pack and move.
嘿 贝丝宝
Hey, Bethy-boo.
是我 艾莉
It's Ellie. Just…
只是打电话问候你一声
calling to say hi.
还有 我和阿捷 我们…
And, um… me and Jay, we, uh…
你知道吗…
You know what--
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
我也很讨厌自己的声音
I hate the sound of my voice too.
你是什么情况 贝丝？
What's going on with you, Beth?
我又闯祸了 就像往常一样
I screwed up again, like I always do.
我需要你帮我解决 做决定
And I need you to help me figure it out.
又需要了
Again.
出什么事了？
What happened?
(嘿 妈妈 你真厉害!)
动作快点 布里奇特
Hurry up, Bridge.
要不你来拿披萨？
You wanna carry them?
要不你去考驾照？
You wanna get your license?
走吧 卡西
Come on, Kass.
地震了！
Earthquake!
来吧
Come on.
快走！
Go!
蹲下！
Stay down!
(方达修树服务)
老天
Shit.
震得真厉害
That was intense.
我觉得我吓尿裤子了
I think I peed my pants.
是热的吗？
Is it warm?
多半只是汽水
It's probably just soda.
好了 走吧
All right. Come on.
(亨丽埃塔披萨店 来吃吧!)
老天 布里奇特 看看这个
Holy shit. Bridget, check this out.
看什么？
What is it?
这里有个洞
There's a hole.
小心 丹 可能会有余震
Careful, Dan. There could be aftershocks.
是个旧的银行金库！
It's an old bank vault!
丹尼 别！
Danny, don't!
丹？
Dan?
来吧 丹尼 我们走吧！
Come on, Danny. Let's go!
稍等一下！
Just hang on!
(三 1923年1月24日)
丹尼！
Danny!
放松点 布里奇特！
Relax a minute, Bridge!
丹尼 你没事吧？
Danny, are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
(圣本笃 保护我们)
打通了吗？
Anything?
完全没有信号
The network is totally screwed.
他们肯定没事的 艾尔
I'm sure they're fine, El.
嘿
Hey.
大家都还好吗？有人受伤吗？
Is everyone okay? Anybody hurt?
嘿 加布
Hey, Gabe.
孩子们去买披萨了 我打不通他们的手机
The kids went to go get pizza
能借你的车去找他们吗？
and I can't get through on their cells. Can I borrow your car to go find them?
-我开车送你去怎么样？ -谢谢
-How about I drive you? -Thanks.
我去拿钥匙
Let me get the keys.
-你是谁？ -贝丝
-Who are you? -Beth.
艾莉的妹妹
Ellie's sister.
对哦 那个骨肉皮
Ah, yeah, yeah. The groupie.
让我问你一件事
Let me ask you somethin'.
你能听到它在上面吗？
Can you hear her up there?
-什么？ -地震
-What? -Quake.
吓得它躲去管道里了
Sent her hiding in the ducts.
快来 小猫咪
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
我们走吧
Let's roll.
是他们吗？
Is that them?
很高兴认识你
Good to meet you.
地震之后绝不该乘电梯
You never take the elevator after a quake.
布里奇特把披萨掉地上了
Bridget dropped the pizza.
宝贝 你们没事就好 谁在乎披萨啊？
Oh, honey. I love you guys so much more than pizza.
不到一小时前
The magnitude 5.5 earthquake
普恩特山断层以北发生了5点5级地震
hit just north of the Puente Hills fault less than an hour ago.
受影响地区包括洛杉矶市中心 以及从拉哈布拉到…
Jolting downtown Los Angeles and everywhere from La Habra to…
你觉得这玩意儿可能值钱吗？
You think it might be worth something?
妈妈现在正需要额外的收入 你不觉得吗？
Mom could do with some extra money right now, don't you think?
我觉得妈妈不会想要 用你偷来的东西换来的钱的
I don't think Mom wants cash from something you stole.
这不是偷来的
It's not stolen.
这多半被锁在那个金库里很久了
It's probably been locked in that vault forever.
没错 而且这样的古怪东西 被锁起来是有原因的
Yeah, and weird shit like this gets locked away for a reason.
别去碰它 丹
Just leave it, Dan.
可恶！
Argh! Fuck!
让我看看
Let me see it.
只是被戳了一下
It's just a nick.
丹
Dan…
丹尼 拜托把它合上吧
Danny, please close it.
丹 我有不祥的预感
I don't like this, Dan.
你得马上把它放回去
You need to put it back right now.
今晚妈妈不会再让我们出门的
Mom's not letting any of us out the front door again tonight.
那就明天一早还
First thing in the morning then.
答应我？
Promise me?
你是要去深海潜水吗？
You going deep sea diving?
进去之前 我得先看看底下有没有东西
I gotta see under before I get in.
我以前在海滩上被水母蜇过
I got stung by a jellyfish at the beach before.
我不喜欢到水下面去
I don't like going underwater.
我不觉得这浴缸里 会有什么古怪的海洋生物
I don't think there's any weird sea creatures in the tub.
哦 我的天！
Oh, my God!
哦 我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
是一个…
It's a… It's a…
你没事吧？
You okay?
我没事 宝贝
I'm good, sweetie.
我也不喜欢肚子痛
I hate when my tummy hurts too.
(一 1923年11月13日)
(播放)
下午好 我的神职同僚
Good afternoon, my fellow clergymen.
我是马库斯利特尔顿神父
I am Father Marcus Littleton,
圣帕特里克大教堂的图书管理员
the library keeper here at Saint Patrick's Cathedral
欢迎大家今天来到天使之城
and I welcome you all today to the City of Angels.
邀请各位来这里
You've been invited here
是想让你们见证 由我们海外传教士发现的
to witness the unveiling of a unique artifact
一件独特文物 这是它的首次公开展示
that was discovered by our overseas missionaries.
我想向各位介绍
I would like to present
我认为是传说中《自然之狂》的
what I believe to be one of the three fabled volumes
三卷之一
of Naturum Demonto,
《死亡之书》
The Book of the Dead.
根据我到目前为止所做的测试
My tests to date have revealed
其镶边由腌人肉制成
that its bindings are made of cured human flesh,
里头的文字及插画 由人血书写绘制而成
its passages and etchings inked in blood.
这是异端之物！
This is heresy!
该书卷显然包含了神圣的奥秘
Today, I seek church approval
今天 我想寻求教会许可 允许我将它翻译出来
to translate the spiritual mysteries its pages undoubtedly hold.
毁掉它！
Destroy it!
它被称为《死亡之书》是有原因的！
It's called The Book of the Dead for a reason!
为了人类的利益 我请求能看看这本书！
I seek to look at this book for the good of man!
(二 1923年1月24日)
被我教会的长老们拒绝之后
Rejected by the elders of our church,
我和达米安沙纳汉教士 及雨果科尔特斯神父
myself, Canon Damien Shanahan, and Father Hugo Cortez
便开始秘密翻译
have been working in secret to translate
《死亡之书》里的大量文字与符号
The Book of the Dead's myriad writings and glyphs.
书中包含了各种古老的仪式及咒语
Its pages contain ancient rituals and incantations
据说诵读这些咒语
the recitation of which
能让你跟我们现知的
proclaim to allow contact with supernatural forces
浅薄世界之外的超自然力量取得联系
that exist beyond the thin veneer of our known world.
(出口)
今天是上帝创世第1923年的1月24日
It is January 24th in the year of our Lord, 1923.
我 马库斯利特尔顿神父 现在将大声朗读
And I, Father Marcus Littleton, shall now commence reading aloud
属灵复活的第一段经文
the first of the spiritual resurrection passages.
(停)
嘿！
Hey!
来人啊！
Help!
帮帮我！
给我闭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
(让地球再次变酷)
没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
这只是停电而已
It's just a blackout.
(二 1923年1月24日)
布里奇特？
Bridget?
你没事吧？
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
看来只有我们这里停电
Looks like it's just us that's out.
是吗？
Really?
妈妈？
Mom?
艾尔 你在睡觉吗？
El, are you sleeping?
她去哪儿了？
Where is she?
妈妈？
Mom?
艾尔？
El?
出什么事了 姐姐？
What's up, sis?
我做了个最美的梦
I had the most beautiful dream.
梦见我们一起坐在高大的森林里
We were together, sitting in a tall forest.
风儿轻爽 鸟儿在歌唱最甜美的…
The wind was clean and the birds were singing the sweetest…
旋律
Melodies.
那天相当完美 而我满脑子想的都是
It was a perfect day and all I could think about
我有多想把你们都切开
was how much I wanted to cut you all open
然后爬进你们的身体 这样我们就能变成一个幸福的家庭
and climb inside your bodies so that we could stay one happy family.
它在我身体里
It's in me.
别让它带走我的孩子们
Don't let it take my babies.
妈妈！
Mom!
布里奇特 把她带回屋里去
Bridget, take her back inside.
快！
Now!
她怎么了 布里奇特？
What's wrong with her, Bridge?
去楼梯那里！快！
Stairs. Go! Go, go, go.
拜托
Come on.
醒醒 艾莉 拜托 快醒醒
Wake up, Ellie. Come on, wake up.
丹尼！
Danny!
楼梯没了
They're gone.
前一分钟她还好好的 突然就开始说疯话 然后…
One minute she was fine and the next she was talking crazy and…
现在她死了
And now she's gone.
还是没有信号
Network's still fucked.
我可以祈祷吗？
May I pray?
她不信教
She's not religious.
生前不信
Wasn't.
只是简单的祈祷
It's just a few words.
一起来吧
Join me.
上帝啊 赐予她永恒的安息
Eternal rest grant unto her, O Lord
让永恒的光芒照耀在她身上
and let perpetual light shine upon her.
愿她的灵魂及所有逝去的信徒的灵魂
May her soul and the souls of all the faithful departed
借着上帝的怜悯…
through the mercy of God
她的脸怎么了？
What the hell happened to her face?
…永远安息
Rest in peace.
像是被人打过一样
Looks like someone beat her up.
在大楼的北侧
There's an old fire-escape ladder
有个旧的消防梯
on the north side of the building.
我可以试着从那里下去 拉响警报 找人过来救援
I could try to get down that, raise the alarm, get some help in here.
去那里得穿过82号公寓
You have to go through 82.
见鬼
Ah, shit.
那里没人住吧？
That's unoccupied, right?
没错 像这垃圾楼里的多数公寓一样
Yeah. Like most of this condemned dump.
你那里有工具
You got the tools?
我们可以直接把门撬开
We could just cut right through the door.
工具在我的卡车里
In my truck.
没重型器具
You ain't gettin' through those old doors
你是撬不开那些旧门的
without something heavy-duty.
我想要爸爸回来
I want Dad to come home.
他会回来的
He will.
手机信号恢复正常后 他就会马上回来
When we get the phones working again, he'll come right back.
你怎么知道他会？
How do you know he will?
你之前还说妈妈会没事的呢
You said Mom was gonna be okay.
我以为她会没事
I thought she would be.
我很抱歉 卡西
I'm so sorry, Kass.
我去拿霰弹枪 直接把锁轰开
I'm gonna get my shotgun, and we're gonna blast it open.
给我一分钟 好吗？
Just give me a minute, okay?
我不喜欢被困
I don't like being trapped.
大家已经够紧张了 不需要枪声来火上浇油
Everyone is on edge enough without guns getting fired in here.
我不知道该怎么办 艾尔
I don't know what to do, El.
你才是那个 总是知道怎么解决问题的人
You're the one who always has the answers.
我现在怕得要命 都不敢面对你的孩子们
I'm too scared to even face your kids right now.
你生前不管有多忙 都总能为我 为所有的人
No matter how busy you ever got, you always found time for me.
抽出时间
For everyone.
真不敢相信我再也不能跟你说话了
I can't believe I'm never gonna speak to you again.
嘿 贝丝宝 是我 艾莉
Hey, Bethy-boo. It's Ellie.
只是打电话问候你一声 还有…
Just… calling to say hi. And, uh…
贝丝！
Beth. Beth!
你得帮帮我 贝丝 你得帮我
You have to help me, Beth. You have to.
我好烫 要被活活烧死了！
I'm burning. I'm burning alive!
艾尔？
El?
-妈妈？ -她还活着？
-Mom? -She's alive?
她烫得不得了
She's burning up.
我去拿冰块
I'll get ice.
妈妈？
Mom?
妈妈已经死翘翘了
Mommy's with the maggots now.
妈妈 别这样！
Mom, stop it!
快停下！
Stop it!
这不是我的错 布里奇特
It's not my fault, Bridget.
离她远点 布里奇特！
Get away from her, Bridge!
宝贝 我这是怎么了？
What's happening to me, sweetheart?
我不知道 妈妈
I don't know, Mom.
我知道
I do.
我现在自由了
I'm free now.
摆脱了你们这些吸奶的寄生虫
Free from all you titty-sucking parasites.
让我亲一下就不疼了
Let me kiss it better.
下一个轮到谁？
Who wants to rot next?
选啊选
Eeny…
挑啊挑
meeny…
这下轮到…
miny…
你
You.
艾莉？
Ellie?
天啊！
Fuck!
把柜子移过来
Grab the cabinet.
离门远点
Get away from the door.
拜托 帮帮我们！
Please, we need help!
让我进去！
Let me in!
喂！
Hello!
能听到我说话吗？
Can you hear me?
你不觉得妈妈的样子 很像那本书里的插画吗？
Don't you think Mom looks just like one of those pictures from that book?
回答我 丹尼
Answer me, Danny.
你就不该把它偷出来
You never should've stolen it.
这不是我的错
This isn't my fault.
这就是你的错！
This is your fault!
-放开我！放开！ -住手！
-Get off me! Get off! - Stop it!
-嘿！行了！ -这都是你的错！
-Hey! Hey, hey! -This is all your fault!
嘿 行了
Hey. Hey.
你们不能自相残杀
You don't turn on each other.
永远都不行
Ever.
我有东西要给你看
I need to show you something.
丹尼 这是什么？
What is this, Danny?
疼得厉害吗？
Does it hurt bad?
布里奇特？
Bridget?
我没事
I'm okay.
♪ 留着卷发的 ♪
♪ Gold-haired girls ♪
♪ 金发女孩们 ♪
♪ With curling tresses ♪
♪ 睡吧 小宝宝 ♪
♪ Hush-a-bye baby ♪
♪ 非我亲生的小宝宝 ♪
♪ Babe not mine ♪
♪ 用悲伤的爱抚 ♪
♪ Mothers who nurse ♪
♪ 哺育孩子的妈妈们 ♪
♪ With sad caresses ♪
♪ 睡吧 小宝宝 ♪
♪ Hush-a-bye baby ♪
♪ 非我亲生的小宝宝 ♪
♪ Babe not mine ♪
妈妈？
Mom?
贝丝？
Beth?
我还拿了这些
I took these too.
里头有个令人毛骨悚然的牧师 在诵读书中的段落
There's this creepy priest on them, reading passages from the book.
像是古怪的邪恶祷文
It's like a weird dark prayer.
当他念诵那段话时…
And when he spoke the words…
布里奇特是对的 这都是我的错
Bridget's right. This is all my fault.
布里奇特
Bridget…
♪ 带上黑刀 ♪
♪ And black knife bring ♪
♪ 抹去我的悲伤 ♪
♪ To cross my sorrow ♪
♪ 睡吧 小宝宝 ♪
♪ Hush-a-bye baby ♪
♪ 非我亲生的小宝宝 ♪
♪ Babe not mine ♪
你来了呀
Oh, there you are.
嘿 小乖乖
Hey there, cutie-pie.
妈妈 你怎么了？
What's wrong with you, Mom?
我只是在为我和你爸的事感到难过
I was just feeling sad about me and your dad.
不过现在他来了
But he's here now.
他回家来看我们了
He came home to see us.
我们要复合了
We're getting back together.
我们彼此相爱
We love each other.
对不对 我亲爱的？
Isn't that right, my darling?
而且我们也爱你
And we love you too.
打开门 卡西 让我们进去
Open up and let us in, Kassie.
我们可以再次成为一个幸福的大家庭
We can be a big, happy family again.
你看上去不太好 妈妈
You don't look so good, Mom.
你给我一个大大的拥抱 再亲亲我 我就会好了
Nothing a big old hug and kiss from you won't fix.
快把门打开
Open up now,
乖 听话
like a good girl.
这就对了
That's it.
快打开
Come on, now.
为爸爸妈妈打开门
Do it for Mom and Dad.
妈妈！
Mom!
-你没事吧？ -对不起
-You okay? -I'm sorry.
我以为妈妈好点了
I thought Mom was better.
像你打开双腿一样把门打开 你这个骨肉皮臭荡妇！
Open the door like you open your legs, you stinking groupie slut!
我不是骨肉皮 你这个变态贱人！
I'm not a groupie, you psycho bitch!
贝丝
Beth.
去你的房间
Go to your room.
会没事的 丹尼
It'll be okay, Danny.
斯塔法尼会保护我们的 对吗？
Staffanie will protect us. Right?
对
Yeah.
你在看什么呢 亲爱的？
What are you looking at, hon?
我得杀死肚子里 那些令人毛骨悚然的爬虫
I gotta kill the creepy-crawlies that I got inside my tummy.
我不喜欢肚子里有东西
I don't like having things inside my tummy.
你呢 贝丝阿姨？
Do you, Auntie Beth?
(“女权主义”不是淫秽的词汇)
嘿
Hey.
这是个噩梦吗？
Is this a nightmare?
这就像一场噩梦 卡西
It's just like a nightmare, Kass.
发生在布里奇特和妈妈身上的事 也会发生在我们身上吗？
Is what happened to Bridget and Mom gonna happen to us?
我不会让这种情况发生的
I'm not gonna let that happen.
我保证
I promise.
贝丝阿姨 有一天你会成为一个好妈妈的
You'd be a good mom someday, Auntie Beth.
是吗？
Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
因为你知道怎么骗小孩子
You know how to lie to kids.
我想着该把她绑起来
I thought I should tie her up.
以防万一
Just in case.
我想听听那黑胶唱片
I wanna listen to that vinyl.
那样做太危险 那些文字…
It's too dangerous. Those words…
是 但或许那里头 也有能结束这一切的文字
Yeah, well, maybe there's words on there that can help stop all of this.
没有电 没法转动唱机转盘
We've got no power to run a turntable.
这个问题我能解决
I can fix that.
(三 1923年1月24日)
我先听了第一张 他是在第二张里念那段话的
I listened to the first and then he spoke the words on the second.
那我就从最后一张开始听吧
I guess I'll start at the other end, then.
给 以防万一
Just in case.
自我诵读这本书到现在 已经两个晚上了
It is now two nights since I read aloud from the book.
我希望了解亡灵世界 并与之交流的想法
My want to understand and commune with the other side
被严重误导了
could not have been more misguided.
这段最后的录音是一个警告
I make this final recording as a warning to whoever next comes into contact
告诫下一个会接触到它邪恶页面的人
with its malignant pages.
《死亡之书》无法被摧毁
Naturum Demonto cannot be destroyed.
如果你发现了它 就把它深埋在我们的秘密保险库里
When you find it, bury it deep in our secret vault,
因为我念的那些文字 释放出了比我最黑暗的噩梦
for the words I uttered have unleashed a demonic entity
还要可怕的恶魔
beyond my darkest nightmare.
布里奇特会像妈妈一样复活吗？
Is Bridget gonna come back like Mom?
我不知道 卡西
I don't know, Kass.
那恶魔首先附身科尔特斯 从里到外侵蚀了他
The demon possessed Cortez first, rotting him from the inside out.
我们试图凭借主的话语的力量 驱除那个恶魔
With the might of our Lord's words, we tried to drive out the foul entity
但它嘲笑了我们的祈祷 然后控制了沙纳汉
but it mocked our prayers and took Shanahan under its control.
其他的神父同胞们赶来帮忙
Fellow priests came to our aid
但他们很快也被附身 而且毫无规律可言
but the possession quickly spread amongst them without rhyme nor reason.
这股邪恶力量不受人类规则的辖制
This evil is not governed by the rules of man.
它以引发彻底混乱、制造恐怖为乐
No, it takes its pleasure in creating terror through total chaos.
我迫切地想终止咒语的效力
Desperate to end this curse,
于是便试图杀死曾是我兄弟的人
I tried to kill what were once my brothers.
我把他们引到柴房里 然后放了把火
I led them to the woodshed and set it ablaze.
但他们却在火焰中跳舞 在焚烧中狂欢
But they danced in its flame and reveled in its burn.
方达先生的小猫有时会躲在那上面
Mr. Fonda's kitty hides up there sometimes.
我觉得那不是猫
I don't think it's a cat.
我将他们蠕动、呕吐的尸体 埋在圣地之下
I buried their squirming, spitting corpses in consecrated earth.
但他们又站了起来 全身腐烂 充满愤怒
But they arose again, rotting and rage-filled.
小心点 丹尼
Careful, Danny.
在地窖里躲了一个晚上之后
After hiding in the cellar for a night
我知道自己只剩下一个选择了
I knew only one choice remained.
彻底肢解
Complete bodily dismemberment.
丹尼 我告诉过你 你该把书还回去的
Told you, you should've put the book back, Danny.
我砍啊 劈啊
I chopped, and I hacked,
还是失败了
and I… I failed.
我现在能听到他们在门外 想要抓到我
I can hear them outside the doors now, begging for me.
我被附身只是早晚的问题
It is only a matter of time before I am taken too.
什么都阻止不了这恶魔般的力量
Nothing can stop this demonic force.
就连它的最后残余也会追捕你
Even its final remnants will come after you.
你必须逃跑
You must run.
你所能做的就是逃跑！
All you can do is run!
这种恐怖会一直继续 直到你不再清白
This horror will not stop until innocence is destroyed.
直到你被
Until evil…
妖魔化为止
…be thy name.
丹尼
Danny.
对不起 卡西
I'm sorry, Kass.
我要吞噬你的灵魂
I will swallow your soul.
有两个灵魂？
Two souls?
别这样 艾尔
Please. El…
艾莉在地狱里 等着你和你未出生的私生子呢
Ellie waits in hell for you and your unborn bastard baby.
不要
No.
贝丝阿姨！
Auntie Beth!
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
你要当妈妈了吗？
Are you gonna be a mom?
是的
Yes.
我会带我们离开这里的
And I'm getting us out of here.
怎么离开？
How?
那个消防梯 我们走
Fire escape. Let's go.
不要回头看那里
Don't look back there.
退后 捂住耳朵
Get back. Cover your ears.
贝丝宝！
Bethy-boo!
卡西 她想把你妈妈从你身边赶走
She's trying to take your mommy away from you, Kassie.
我知道你已经不再是我妈妈了
I know you're not my mom anymore.
别把我从他们身边赶走
Don't take me from them.
贝丝 你不知道 把孩子带到这世界上是什么感觉
You have no idea what it's like to bring a child into this world, Beth.
那是我的枪 你个偷东西的贱人
That's my gun, you thieving cunt.
贝丝阿姨！
Auntie Beth!
这里的每个人 都会在黎明前死去 贝丝
Everybody here dies by dawn, Beth.
快跑！
Run!
在黎明前死去！
Dead by dawn!
-在黎明前死去！ -在黎明前死去！
-Dead by dawn! -By dawn!
在黎明前死去！
Dead by dawn!
给我
Here.
无路可逃！
No way out!
-贝丝阿姨！ -过来！
-Auntie Beth! -Come here!
不要！
No!
(最大负载 6个人或408公斤)
卡西
Kassie. Kassie.
Kassie. Kassie. Kassie.
我死了吗？
Am I dead?
(世界公寓)
快 上车
Come on. Get in.
卡西 开门的遥控器在哪儿？
Kass, where's the beeper?
拜托
Come on. Come on.
它来了
It's coming.
钻进去！
Get under!
卡西！
Kassie!
(方达修树服务)
我只想要你的小脑袋 宝贝女儿
All I want is your little head, baby girl.
来吃枪子吧
Come get some.
(停)
卡西 把机器打开！
Turn it on, Kass!
求你了
Please.
救救我 贝丝宝
Help me, Bethy-boo.
只有我姐才能那样叫我
Only my sister gets to call me that.
要知道 你长得真的很像妈妈
You know, you really do look like Mom.
而且你会像她一样悲惨地失败的
And you're gonna fail miserably just like her.
你这个又臭又可怕的贱货骨肉皮！
You stinking, horrible…groupie cunt!
(出口 推杆开门)
之前一直都没手机信号 五分钟前刚恢复
There's been no cell signal until, like, five minutes ago
雷声吵得我无法入睡 所以我根本没睡
and the thunder kept me awake, so I got basically less than zero sleep.
不管怎样 虽然我一大早满腹牢骚
Anyway, all my early morning moans aside,
我们还是会在湖边度过美好周末的
we are still gonna have such a fab weekend at the lake.
迦勒爸爸的小屋很棒
Caleb's dad's cabin is so awesome,
而且你会很喜欢他的朋友们的
and you're gonna absolutely love his friends.
我相信其中一个会跟你很般配
I'm sure one of them will be perfect for you.
我不想扫你的兴
I don't mean to be a downer or anything
但我其实在考虑这次不去
but I was actually thinking of taking a rain check
改期再去
on this whole trip thing.
门都没有
Not a chance.
我15分钟后来接你
I'm picking you up in 15.
回头见！
Bye!